[
    {
        "question": "Why did the web designer drown?",
        "answer": "She didnâ€™t know if she should float:left or float:right",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was the web developer fired from his job?",
        "answer": "They were getting to SASSy",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what does a developer do at the end of a group project?",
        "answer": "gits committed",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is HackerYou's favourite react expression?",
        "answer": "DIV DADDDIII",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you comfort a javascript bug?",
        "answer": "You console it",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the Web Developer pay an extra few bucks to their hosting provider?",
        "answer": "Because he heard that he should always tip his server",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "How did pirates collab before computers",
        "answer": "Pier to Pier programming",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the Front-End Web Developer do when he got to the beach?",
        "answer": "Display: flex",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the developers go broke?",
        "answer": "they used up all their cache",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was the Javascript developer sad?",
        "answer": "Because they didn't NODE how to express themself",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the Javascript developer get lost?",
        "answer": "Forgot how to use map",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the object-oriented way to become weathy",
        "answer": "Inheritance",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the programmer quit their job?",
        "answer": "Didn't get arrays",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "The developer successfully completed a react project",
        "answer": "PROPS",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Why are so many react developers anarchists?",
        "answer": "Because they want to keep everything stateless",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the Front-End Web Developer do when he got to the beach?",
        "answer": "Display: flex",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Javascript call his son",
        "answer": "JSON",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was the function sad after the first call",
        "answer": "Didn't get a callback",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "total": 0,
        "id": 17
    }
]